[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "How bad was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "You can Google it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "You enjoy the status of television icon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Oh, well, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "You're that guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How does it go down with all your famous friends?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well, some of my --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Is it lonely out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "It's pretty lonely, but you know they seem to tolerate me somehow, because I can at least state myself eloquently and without actually kind of assuming what they -- the veneer of what they assume is what a Republican is, as some kind of nasty, strange villain that, you know, should be vilified and hated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "So, you did do the hard yards of theatrical trainings, didn't you, to be a serious actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Did you ever imagine at that stage, at Juilliard, you're looking around, all these talented people presumably -- did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams or maybe nightmares the level of fame that you would one day get through acting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Juilliard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "And in the back of your mind all you're thinking of is this could tank, and then what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "You trained with him at the Julliard, didn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Yes, we were together in school.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Julliard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "But is part of that because you've managed to deal with so many of the demons that you carry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", ":", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What was the -- what was the wake up moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, there were -- there were several along the way, where I just -- you know, I'd sit there and say, I've got to stop.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Betty Ford"]}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "How did you manage to stop in the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Well, actually, I did go to Betty Ford, and that helped.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I have a drink sometimes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "You can drink in moderation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "How did it feel to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "It's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Did she fire a gun at you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "That was another night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 286, "question": "You married her after she shot at you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes, no, this is the -- this is what --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Wasn't that a warning sign, get off it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "WDT", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I tell you, it was absurdly across -- a shot across the bow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "A woman shoots at me, I'm thinking twice about the marriage, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "So that fell apart pretty quickly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "This must have been like hell, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Well, I have to -- I mean, I have to tell you, my -- \"The Real Housewives\" was my parting gift to her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "But -- I mean, how are things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, they're not good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Do you have any kind of dialogue with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "We have no contact, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "How is your relationship with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Oh, it's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "You get plenty of access?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, they're trying to -- they're doing their best to actually kind of make that difficult for me right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Do you think she married you because you were Kelsey Grammer, TV icon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "No, I think she married me because I was Frasier.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kelsey Grammer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I think it was Frasier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What's been worst thing, the most hurtful thing she said about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, you know, I haven't been keeping track of everything, so there might be something that would surprise me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "What's the most unfair labeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "She once said that I didn't want my daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Yes, well, it would, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "To England from New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "From Los Angeles.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "From Los Angeles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kayte"]}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Well, you know what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Because Kayte is a very beautiful young lady, as we can see here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Did she know who you were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Oh, I think she knew who I was, but she didn't know who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What is it about her you think that enabled her to deal with all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "She believes in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Are you really enjoying it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "It's been -- it was a presumptive joining (ph) of the work every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Do you like him or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I love him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Isn't that you, in the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Do you feel for the first you've gone back to the joy of life you had as a young boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "RAMMER: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Ma, can I go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "How are you feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "I feel great, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I feel like -- across the years, it's been, like, mixed emotions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "And did your mom always have this inkling you had what it took?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Do you feel you missed out on anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "What do you feel that you missed on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Stupid things like passing notes in school and having a locker and riding the bus, I mean, really stupid things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "It can be lonely, can't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ":"], "qSentId": 697, "question": "And I think I was good at separating that and being, like, OK, well, they get this, but I get this, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBG", ",", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "If your little boy gets to about 8 or 9...", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "... I want to be star, how can you stop it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Oh, it's so hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Why would you be so concerned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "From when I started to now, the industry is so different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "What is the least perfect thing about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "Oh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "You couldn't find anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "For you, the halo is, like, clasped on your head.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "What did you call Faye Dunaway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Oh, this is a long time ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Faye Dunaway"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "How bad was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "You can Google it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Do you believe in love at first sight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "I'll let you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "How could I have seen you before and not know who you are now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "Maybe you were looking, but you weren't really seeing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "I mean, you've made a lot of money, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "I have done quite well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "And said to her -- (INAUDIBLE) remind what you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", ":", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Do you like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "Yes, I love that!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 796, "question": "Did it keep her quiet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 797, "answer": "Well, she came back and said, you know, Oh, I never made that comment, and blah, blah, blah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "I mean, why would she say that to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "ORGAN: Well, I'm all for feuds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Now, how many terrible frogs did you have to kiss before you got to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "Quite a few.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Who has the worst list, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Oh, him by far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "Didn't you have Kim Kardashian on the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "I don't think even hers is bigger than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kim Kardashian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 848, "question": "Is that what he gave you as an engagement ring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 849, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "Yes, I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "Did you actually write this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]